fiat500.com 2017-07-10

# Privacy Policy | Fiat

## GENERAL INTRODUCTION

This Policy is intended to describe the management of this site owned by FCA Italy S.p.A., in relation to the processing of this website’s users / visitors personal data.

FCA Italy S.p.A., in line with the current Italian data protection law, undertakes to guarantee the privacy and the security of each website navigator's personal data, even when the Internet is accessed from abroad, consistently with the requirements of the Group Code of Conduct. 

The Policy is also given as a short disclosure statement, if a specific detailed one is not provided, pursuant to Article 13 of Legislative Decree 196/03 – Personal Data Protection Code, issued in application of Art. 10 and 11 from European Directive 95/46/CE, to those who interact with the website services, with the purpose of protecting personal data accessible by computer. 

Detailed information regarding processing, as per Article 13 of Legislative Decree 196/03 – Personal Data Protection Code - is provided, where necessary, in the pages where services are offered. These disclosure statements aim to define the data processing limits and procedures for each service so that the customer/visitor may freely provide consent and authorise collection of his/her personal data and its subsequent use. 

Please note that the disclosure statement will not be provided for other websites possibly accessed by the user through links.

## DATA CONTROLLER, DATA PROCESSORS AND DATA PROCESSING OFFICERS OF THE DATA PROCESSING

The Data Controller is the interim manager of the Information & Communication Technologies department of FCA Italy S.p.A., with registered office in Turin, Corso Agnelli 200, Italy. 

The Data Processor for this Service is the interim manager of Brand Marketing Communication Department of FCA Italy S.p.A.. 

The personal data that you have provided may be handled by Data Processing Officers, including external, responsible for managing the requested service and by Data Processor(s).

## TYPE OF DATA PROCESSED AND PURPOSE OF TREATMENT

This website offers informative and interactive content. During site navigation, information regarding the customer, or more generally regarding the visitor to the site, may be acquired as follows: 

**Navigation data**

During normal operation, the IT systems and software procedures used to run this site collect some personal data, which are implicitly transmitted through the use of Internet communication protocols. 

This information is not collected in order to be associated with identified data subjects, but could, due to their own nature, and if processed and integrated with third-party data, allow Users to be identified. 

IP addresses, browser type, operating system, domain name and website referring or exit pages, information on pages visited by the User within the site, access time, navigation length on each page, clickstream analysis and other parameters regarding the operating system and the user IT environment, all fall under this category of data. 

This technical/IT data are collected and used on an aggregated and anonymous basis exclusively to improve quality of service and obtain statistics on site use. 

This technical data/information are collected and used in an aggregated and anonymous way for the sole purpose of:  
1\. Improving the quality of the service and optimize the functionality of the site;   
2\. understanding user behavior in order to improve online communication;  
3\. providing statistical information concerning the use of the site

**Geolocation data**

Subject to the prior consent of the visitor, the web site will be able to deal with location data - in a non-continuous - to provide the services requested by the visitor. 

**Data voluntarily supplied by the customer/visitor**

These cases involve the customer/visitor entering his/her personal data on the site after reading detailed information in order to access personally selected services. 

"Opt-in" and "Opt-out" policies: in all cases, appropriate detailed information is provided and, where required, consent for the processing of personal data is obtained before a given service is activated. Said consent may be revoked at any time, whereby the ability to use the service in question is lost. 

Specific information is gradually provided or displayed on pages of the site that offer specific services on request. 

**Data from minors**

FCA Italy S.p.A. does not allow minors under 18 years of age to supply personal data.

## DATA PROCESSING RULES

The data processing will be performed through automated means (ie. using electronic procedures) and/or manually (ie. on paper) for the time necessary to achieve the purposes for which the data were collected and in compliance with current data protection law.

## TECHNOLOGIES

 **Cookies**

The use of cookies by this site is governed by Cookie Policy. 

**Web beacons, clear GIFs, page tags e web bugs**

These are all terms used to describe specific technologies used by our website to help us understand and analyze how they are used and to improve the website experience. They can be used for promotional messages sent on the pages visited. 

A web beacon (or similar) corresponds to a small transparent image, attached to a web page or email. It is used in conjunction with cookies and send information such as IP address, when the web page or the email is displayed, from which device and which region. 

As part of the web page, you can not delete them, but you can make them unusable by disabling cookies on their setup. 

**Javascript**

This is a technique used as an alternative to direct analysis of Web server log files. It consists of collecting and processing navigation data using dedicated JavaScript code in the HTML pages deemed of interest.

## SUBJECTS CAN BE AWARE OF YOUR DATA

Your personal data may be processed by other persons acting on behalf of FCA Italy S.p.A., under specific contractual obligations in EU Member States or in countries outside the EU, and within the limits provided for by articles 43 and 44 letter b) of Legislative Decree no. n. 196/2003. 

Your personal information may be disclosed to third parties to fulfill legal obligations, or to comply with orders from public authorities or to exercise a right in court.

## CONNECTION TO THIRD PARTY SITES

It is possible to link to other websites from this site; the ability to do so is clearly indicated in order to inform the user/visitor that he/she is leaving the FCA Italy S.p.A. site. 

The user/visitor should note that these sites are not the property or responsibility of FCA Italy S.p.A. as they are fully managed by other companies and/or organizations. 

It is therefore necessary to verify and accept their data protection policies. 

FCA Italy S.p.A. consequently declines all responsibility for requests and/or release of personal data to third-party sites.

## RIGHTS OF INTERESTED PARTIES

The data subject has the right at any time to obtain confirmation of the existence of the data and to know its contents and origin, to check its accuracy or request integration, updating or correction (Art. 7 of Legislative Decree 196/03). 

Pursuant to this Article the data subject has the right to request the complete and updated list of all the data processors, to request cancellation, anonimyzation or blocking of data that have been processed unlawfully and may refuse, for legitimate reasons, their processing. 

To exercise these rights and in case of any problem or further requests for clarification related to what above mentioned, please write to FCA Italy S.p.A. – Customer Experience & CRM – Ufficio Privacy - C.so Agnelli 200 - 10135 Torino.

## POLICY CHANGES

This Privacy Policy governs the methods for processing personal data provided by users/visitors when navigating our website. These methods may need to be modified as a result of new laws entering into force or after examination and updating of User services. As a result, our policy may be modified over time, and we kindly ask customers/visitors to periodically consult this page.

Data: 09 Aprile 2015
